
const questions = [
    {
        Harry_Potter: [
            {
                id: 1,
                question: "What is Harry Potter's dad first name?",
                answer1: "John",
                answer2: "Tom",
                answer3: "Michael",
                answer4: "Harry",
                correct: "John",
                correctNumber: "answer1"
            },
            {
                id : 2,
                question: "How old is Voldermor?",
                answer1: 50,
                answer2: 39,
                answer3: 69,
                answer4: 100,
                correct: 50,
                correctNumber: "answer1"
            }
        ],
        Games_of_Chance: [
            {
                id: 1,
                question: "Seb is scared away from hockey after injuring his:",
                answer1: "Head",
                answer2: "Arm",
                answer3: "Leg",
                answer4: "Collarbone",
                correct: "Collarbone",
                correctNumber: "answer4"
            },
            {
                id: 2,
                question: "What is Alex's usual drink at the Looch?",
                answer1: "Scotch and soda",
                answer2: "Gin and tonic",
                answer3: "Whiskey sour",
                answer4: "Negroni",
                correct: "Gin and tonic",
                correctNumber: "answer2"
            },
            {
                id: 3,
                question: "Emilia works at which company?",
                answer1: "Adidas",
                answer2: "Under Armour",
                answer3: "Puma",
                answer4: "Nike",
                correct: "Nike",
                correctNumber: "answer4"
            },
            {
                id: 4,
                question: "Where did Maureen grow up?",
                answer1: "Newark, NJ",
                answer2: "Gardenbook, NJ",
                answer3: "Bensonhurst, Brooklyn",
                answer4: "Bedford-Stuyvesant, Brooklyn",
                correct: "Bensonhurst, Brooklyn",
                correctNumber: "answer3"
            },
            {
                id: 5,
                question: "Which stuffed animal does Seb hide in his backpack?",
                answer1: "Bear",
                answer2: "Bunny",
                answer3: "Tiger",
                answer4: "Panda",
                correct: "Bunny",
                correctNumber: "answer2"
            },
            {
                id: 6,
                question: "What's the name of the concert venue where Jenn and Alex first start dating?",
                answer1: "The Looch",
                answer2: "Sullivan's",
                answer3: "The Fishbowl",
                answer4: "Titan",
                correct: "The Fishbowl",
                correctNumber: "answer3"
            },
            {
                id: 7,
                question: "Emilia's best friend in college, with whom she has a big falling out, is:",
                answer1: "Ashley",
                answer2: "Aubrey",
                answer3: "Casey",
                answer4: "Amanda",
                correct: "Aubrey",
                correctNumber: "answer2"
            },
            {
                id: 8,
                question: "What is Bedhead's real name?",
                answer1: "Joe Murphy",
                answer2: "Jon Sullivan",
                answer3: "Nicky Bacio",
                answer4: "Frankie Vitelli",
                correct: "Jon Sullivan",
                correctNumber: "answer2"
            },
            {
                id: 9,
                question: "What is Alex's favorite song?",
                answer1: "Layla",
                answer2: "Fly",
                answer3: "Born to Run",
                answer4: "American Girl",
                correct: "Fly",
                correctNumber: "answer2"
            },
            {
                id: 10,
                question: "What was Seb and Emilia's original last name?",
                answer1: "Bruno",
                answer2: "Romano",
                answer3: "Caruso",
                answer4: "D'Angelo",
                correct: "Caruso",
                correctNumber: "answer3"
            }
        ]
    }]

export {questions};